Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
- The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.34:no.33 (1930: Aug. 14)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.34:no.34 (1930: Aug. 21)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.34:no.35 (1930: Aug. 28)
- The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.36 (1930: Sept. 4)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.37 (1930: Sept. 11)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.38 (1930: Sept. 18)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.39 (1930: Sept. 25)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.40 (1930: Oct. 2)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.41 (1930: Oct. 9)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.41A (1930: Oct. 10)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.42 (1930: Oct. 16)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.43 (1930: Oct. 23)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.44 (1930: Oct. 30)
- The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.45 (1930: Nov. 6)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.45A (1930: Nov. 7)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.46 (1930: Nov. 13)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.47 (1930: Nov. 20)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.48 (1930: Nov. 27)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.49 (1930: Dec. 4)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.50 (1930: Dec. 11)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.51 (1930: Dec. 18)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1930; Publication (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.52 (1930: Dec. 25)
- The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.1 (1931: Jan. 1)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.2 (1931: Jan. 8)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.3 (1931: Jan. 15)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.4 (1931: Jan. 22)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.5 (1931: Jan. 29)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.6 (1931: Feb. 5)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.7 (1931: Feb. 12)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.8 (1931: Feb. 19)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.9 (1931: Feb. 26)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.10 (1931: Mar. 5)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.11 (1931: Mar. 12)
  - Item 12: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.12 (1931: Mar. 19)
  - Item 13: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.13 (1931: Mar. 26)
  - Item 14: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.14 (1931: Apr. 2)
  - Item 15: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.15 (1931: Apr. 9)
  - Item 16: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.15A (1931: Apr. 10)
  - Item 17: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.16 (1931: Apr. 16)
  - Item 18: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.17 (1931: Apr. 23)
  - Item 19: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.35:no.18 (1931: Apr. 30)
- The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.19 (1931: May 7)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.20 (1931: May 14)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.21 (1931: May 21)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.22A (1931: May 23)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.22 (1931: May 28)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.23 (1931: June 4)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.24 (1931: June 11)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.25 (1931: June 18)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.26 (1931: June 25)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.27 (1931: July 2)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.28 (1931: July 9)
  - Item 12: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.29 (1931: July 16)
  - Item 13: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.30 (1931: July 23)
  - Item 14: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.31 (1931: July 30)
  - Item 15: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.32 (1931: Aug. 6)
  - Item 16: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.33 (1931: Aug. 13)
  - Item 17: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.34 (1931: Aug. 20)
  - Item 18: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.35 (1931: Aug. 27)
  - Item 19: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.36 (1931: Sept. 3)
- The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.37 (1931: Sept. 10)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.38 (1931: Sept. 17)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.39 (1931: Sept. 24)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.39A (1931: Sept. 25)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.40 (1931: Oct. 1)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.41 (1931: Oct. 8)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.42 (1931: Oct. 15)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.43 (1931: Oct. 22)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.44 (1931: Oct. 29)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.45 (1931: Nov. 5)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.46 (1931: Nov. 12)
  - Item 12: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.47 (1931: Nov. 19)
  - Item 13: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.48 (1931: Nov. 26)
  - Item 14: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.49 (1931: Dec. 3)
  - Item 15: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.50 (1931: Dec. 10)
  - Item 16: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.51 (1931: Dec. 17)
  - Item 17: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.51, Part 2 (1931: Dec. 17)
  - Item 18: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.52 (1931: Dec. 24)
  - Item 19: The National Underwriter, 1931; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.53 (1931: Dec. 31)
- The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.1 (1932: Jan. 7)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.2 (1932: Jan. 14)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.3 (1932: Jan. 21)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.4 (1932: Jan. 28)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.5 (1932: Feb. 4)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.6 (1932: Feb. 11)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.7 (1932: Feb. 18)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.8 (1932: Feb. 25)
- The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.9 (1932: Mar. 3)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.10 (1932: Mar. 10)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.11 (1932: Mar. 17)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.12 (1932: Mar. 24)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.13 (1932: Mar. 31)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.14 (1932: Apr. 7)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.15 (1932: Apr. 14)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.15A (1932: Apr. 15)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.16 (1932: Apr. 21)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.17 (1932: Apr. 28)
- The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.18 (1932: May 5)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.19 (1932: May 12)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.20 (1932: May 19)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.21 (1932: May 26)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.22 (1932: June 2)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.23 (1932: June 9)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.23A (1932: June 10)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.24 (1932: June 16)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.25 (1932: June 23)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.36:no.26 (1932: June 30)
- The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.27 (1932: July 7)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.28 (1932: July 14)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.29 (1932: July 21)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.30 (1932: July 28)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.31 (1932: Aug. 4)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.32 (1932: Aug. 11)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.32A (1932: Aug. 13)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.33 (1932: Aug. 18)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.34 (1932: Aug. 25)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.35 (1932: Sept. 1)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.36 (1932: Sept. 8)
  - Item 12: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.37 (1932: Sept. 15)
  - Item 13: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.38 (1932: Sept. 22)
  - Item 14: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.38A (1932: Sept. 23)
  - Item 15: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.39 (1932: Sept. 29)
- The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.40 (1932: Oct. 6)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.41 (1932: Oct. 13)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.42 (1932: Oct. 20)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.43 (1932: Oct. 27)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.44 (1932: Nov. 3)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.45 (1932: Nov. 10)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.46 (1932: Nov. 17)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1932; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.47 (1932: Nov. 20)
- New York State Education, 1940-1941 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York State Education, 1940; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Author: New York State Teachers Association
    Notes: Index to vol.28, October 1940 - June 1941.
  - Item 2: New York State Education, 1940; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.1 (1940: Oct.)
  - Item 3: New York State Education, 1940; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.2 (1940: Nov.)
  - Item 4: New York State Education, 1940; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.3 (1940: Dec.)
  - Item 5: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.4 (1941: Jan.)
  - Item 6: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.5 (1941: Feb.)
  - Item 7: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.6 (1941: Mar.)
  - Item 8: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.7 (1941: Apr.)
  - Item 9: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.8 (1941: May)
  - Item 10: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.9 (1941: June)
- New York State Education, 1941-1942 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1941: Oct.)
  - Item 2: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.2 (1941: Nov.)
  - Item 3: New York State Education, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.3 (1941: Dec.)
  - Item 4: New York State Education, 1942; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.4 (1942: Jan.)
  - Item 5: New York State Education, 1942; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.5 (1942: Feb.)
  - Item 6: New York State Education, 1942; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.5 (1942: Feb.) Copy 2.
  - Item 7: New York State Education, 1942; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.6 (1942: Mar.)
  - Item 8: New York State Education, 1942; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.7 (1942: Apr.)
- New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940-1941 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Author: Transport Union of America
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1940: June 15)
  - Item 2: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1940: June 22)
  - Item 3: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1940: June 29)
  - Item 4: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1940: July 6)
  - Item 5: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1940: July 13)
  - Item 6: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1940: July 20)
  - Item 7: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1940: Aug. 3)
  - Item 8: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1940: Aug. 10)
  - Item 9: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.10 (1940: Aug. 17)
  - Item 10: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.11 (1940: Aug. 24)
  - Item 11: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.12 (1940: Aug. 31)
  - Item 12: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.13 (1940: Sept. 7)
  - Item 13: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.14 (1940: Sept. 14)
  - Item 14: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.15 (1940: Sept. 21)
  - Item 15: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.16 (1940: Sept. 28)
  - Item 16: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.17 (1940: Oct. 5)
  - Item 17: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.18 (1940: Oct. 12)
  - Item 18: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.19 (1940: Oct. 19)
  - Item 19: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.20 (1940: Oct. 26)
  - Item 20: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.21 (1940: Nov. 2)
  - Item 21: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.22 (1940: Nov. 9)
  - Item 22: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.23 (1940: Nov. 16)
  - Item 23: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.24 (1940: Nov. 23)
  - Item 24: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.25 (1940: Nov. 30)
  - Item 25: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.26 (1940: Dec. 7)
  - Item 26: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.27 (1940: Dec. 14)
  - Item 27: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.28 (1940: Dec. 21)
  - Item 28: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.29 (1940: Dec. 28)
  - Item 29: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.30 (1941: Jan. 4)
  - Item 30: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.31 (1941: Jan. 11)
  - Item 31: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.32 (1941: Jan. 18)
  - Item 32: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.33 (1941: Jan. 25)
  - Item 33: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.34 (1941: Feb. 1)
  - Item 34: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.35 (1941: Feb. 8)
  - Item 35: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.36 (1941: Feb. 15)
  - Item 36: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.37 (1941: Feb. 22)
  - Item 37: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.38 (1941: Mar. 1)
  - Item 38: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.39 (1941: Mar. 8)
  - Item 39: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.40 (1941: Mar. 15)
  - Item 40: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.41 (1941: Mar. 22)
  - Item 41: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.42 (1941: Mar. 29)
  - Item 42: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.43 (1941: Apr. 5)
  - Item 43: New York Weekly Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.44 (1941: Apr. 12)
- Office and Professional News, 1942; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Office and Professional News, 1942; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Author: United Office and Professional Workers of America
    Notes: v.8:no.13 (1942: July 1)
  - Item 2: Office and Professional News, 1942; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.17 (1942: Sept. 1)
  - Item 3: Office and Professional News, 1942; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.18 (1942: Sept. 15)
  - Item 4: Office and Professional News, 1942; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.19 (1942: Oct. 1)
  - Item 5: Office and Professional News, 1942; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.20 (1942: Oct. 15)
  - Item 6: Office and Professional News, 1942; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.21 (1942: Nov.)